

ELCHIN HUMBATOV

FRONT END DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Hi there!

I am a certified and experienced front-end developer.

I have experience in creating mobile responsive web sites, SPA (single page applications). I also have experience in developing a websites from scratch with React and Angular.

LINKS



Github: /elchinhumbatov



Hackerrank: /elchinhumbatov



Linkedin: /in/elchinhumbatov

CONTACT DETAILS



+99550 231 22 97



elchinhumbatov@yahoo.com



bit.ly/elchincv



Baki, Azerbaijan

INTERESTS











PROFESSIONAL CAREER

Customer Retention & Contact Center Support specialist Azercell LLC (2020 - Present)

- Preparing test cases and execute them, then prepared the test results and comments.
- Solving internal problems that came from our CC employees.
- Manage projects, request software changes to facilitate the work of

Front End developer

Benzeine (2021 - Present)

- Maintaining the Angular projects, add new features.
- Create new React project with Redux state manager.
- Writing, refactoring, debugging the code.

B2B Contact Center Senior Representative

Azercell LLC (2016 - 2020)

- Identifying customers needs, clarify information, research every issue and providing solutions.

Contact Center Representative

ABC Telecom LLC (2015 - 2016)

- Obtains client information by answering telephone calls.
- Determines eligibility by comparing client information to requirements.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

STEP IT Computer Academy

Front End Developer (2019-2020)

- Studying Front-End Development.
- Practiced with acquired knowledge

Azerbaijan State Oil Academy

Bachelor degree (2010 - 2014)

- Graduated from the faculty of Geophysics.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS













Angular

React

JavaScript

- HTML, CSS, SCSS, jQuery, Git/Github/Gitlab, React-Redux and many other libraries.
- Bootstrap, Materialize
- Basics: Java, SQL

SOFT SKILLS

- Strong in Communication, Team Work.
- Working on Project Management, Leadership skills.